### Contact

itstannus@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tanvi-shinde-band-72a40320 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Core Java

Java

Multithreading

## Languages

Marathi (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional) Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Cognizant Certified Student SEED Infotech Certified 'JAVA Developer'

# **Tanvi Shinde Band**

Artificial Intelligence | Machine Learning | Deep Learning | Pune

## Summary

I have completed my graduation as a Computer Engineer from MIT College of Engineering, Pune in 2014.

Currently I am working in Adtech domain with Cognologix (4info) on the Demand Side Platform (DSP).

Previously had worked with Personagraph (an Intertrust company) in the same domain, Adtech, on Supply Side platform (SSP) and have delivered various product features on PG Axis platform.

As part of the above, I have been able to acquire proficiency in latest technologies which includes Core java, Collections, Multithreading, Spring, Hibernate, Angular 5, SQL, Design patterns, REST APIs, DropWizard, Maven, Liquibase, Apache Kafka, Apache Spark, Redis, ElasticSearch.

I have done my internship at BMC Software while working on BMC Remedy Incident Management Software. I am aware about the working of Action Request System(AR System) and familiar with AR System Plugin framework. I am also familiar BMC Remedy AR Java API.

I am familiar with ETL tool Informatica 9.5.1 and reporting tool like IBM Cognos version 10.1.

I am hands on with technologies like core java, web services, database, business intelligence tools.

I am good at logical problem solving, data structures and algorithms, operating systems and databases.

I am more inclined towards development role.

I am a quick learner.

## Experience

PubMatic Software Engineer July 2018 - June 2019 (1 year) Pune Area, India

Cognologix Technologies
Full Stack Developer
May 2017 - June 2018 (1 year 2 months)
Pune Area, India

Personagraph Software Engineer July 2016 - April 2017 (10 months) Mumbai Area, India

# Infosys System Engineer Trainee July 2014 - July 2015 (1 year 1 month)

- Business Intelligence Project, System Engineer Trainee: Analysis of Infosys feature InfyTV. Analysis involved data gathering from MySql database, cleaning and organizing using Informatica. The Results were displayed on a dashboard using Cognos BI which helped Infosys managers to make important and informed decisions for managing InfyTv product offering.
- RainStor Archival Project, Test Engineer: Testing the entire process of data archival from Teradata to RainStor, consisting of Informatica workflows, using Unix.

BMC Software Project Intern August 2013 - June 2014 (11 months)

"Audio Video Enabled IT Service Management"

• Worked with BMC software team as a summer intern during graduation to make a Multi-Media (Audio-Video) enabled ITSM app for mobile phones using android which provided interactive platform for raising and resolving internal BMC incidents. This helped BMC softwares in incident detection and resolution.

Technology used:Android,Java,SQLite

MITCOE,Kothrud student March 2010 - June 2014 (4 years 4 months) Kothrud, Pune

Computer engineering

# Education

MITCOE, Kothrud, Pune

Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Computer Engineering · (2010 - 2014)

The Bishops Jr. College 12th, Science (2008 - 2010)

St. Helenas

10th, Computer Science · (1996 - 2008)